<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<odoo>
    <data noupdate="1">
        <!--DEPARTMENT DEMO DATA -->
        <record id="demo_data_course_21" model="academy.course">
            <field name="course_name">MBA Master of Business Administration</field>
            <field name="course_description">
                An MBA is a graduate business degree focused on management, business, and entrepreneurship.
            </field>
        </record>

        <record id="demo_data_course_22" model="academy.course">
            <field name="course_name">MCA Master of Computer Application</field>
            <field name="course_description">
                The Master of Computer Application (MCA) is a professional post-graduate program. Students who take
                admission in this course study computer programs, developing software, computer application development,
                and many other topics in this course. The duration of this course is 2 years.
            </field>
        </record>

        <record id="demo_data_course_23" model="academy.course">
            <field name="course_name">B.COM Bachelor of Commerce</field>
            <field name="course_description">
                BCom is a three-year undergraduate degree that focuses on commerce, economics, business law,
                accountancy, taxation, and financing.
            </field>
        </record>

        <record id="demo_data_course_24" model="academy.course">
            <field name="course_name">B.Ed Bachelor of Education</field>
            <field name="course_description">
                The Bachelor of Education (B.Ed.) degree is a professional program that educates teachers for upper
                primary or intermediate level, secondary, and upper-secondary level.
            </field>
        </record>

        <record id="demo_data_course_25" model="academy.course">
            <field name="course_name">BCA Bachelor of Computer Applications</field>
            <field name="course_description">
                BCA is Bachelor's in Computer Application, which is a 3-year undergraduate degree programme that focuses
                on knowledge of the basics of computer application and software development.
            </field>
        </record>

        <record id="demo_data_course_26" model="academy.course">
            <field name="course_name">BBA Bachelor of Business Administration.</field>
            <field name="course_description">
                A Bachelor of Business Administration (BBA) is a bachelor's degree that helps you establish a
                fundamental understanding of business and how various aspects of it apply to the real world.
            </field>
        </record>

        <record id="demo_data_course_27" model="academy.course">
            <field name="course_name">M.COM Master of Commerce.</field>
            <field name="course_description">
                Master of Commerce (MCom or M Comm; sometimes Magister Commercii as (MagComm or Mag. comm.) is a
                postgraduate master's degree focusing on commerce-, accounting-, management- and economics-related
                subjects.
            </field>
        </record>
    </data>
</odoo>

